<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CoffeeCom</string>

    <!--==========================HOME PAGE==========================-->
    <string name="home_title">Find the best coffee for you</string>
    <string name="current_location">your current location is</string>

    <!--==========================WALLET===========================-->
    <string name="balance">Coffee Balance</string>
    <string name="title_activity_bank_card">BankCardActivity</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="title_activity_wallet_pin">WalletPinActivity</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">MapsActivity</string>
    <string name="PrivacyPolicy">This Privacy Policy describes how we collects, uses, and shares information about you when you use our mobile application (Coffee Community). \n\nWe may change our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain Services, email notification of privacy policy changes). We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy whenever you access the Services to stay informed about our information practices and the choices available to you. \n\n[Information We Collect] \n\nWe collect information about you when you use the App, including when you create an account, place an order, or participate in promotions or surveys. \n\nThe types of information we may collect include: \n\n- Personal information, such as your name, email address, and phone number \n- Payment information, such as credit card details \n- Location data, such as your device location when you use the App \n- Device information, such as your device ID and type, and IP address \n- Usage data, such as information about how you use the App \n\n[How We Use Your Information] \n\nWe use the information we collect to operate, maintain, and improve the App, and to provide the services and features offered through the App. This includes using the information to: \n\n- Process and fulfill your orders \n- Communicate with you about your orders and the App \n- Personalize your experience on the App \n- Understand and analyze trends, usage, and activities in connection with the App \n- Develop new products, services, features, and functionality \n- Protect the security and integrity of the App \n\n[Sharing Your Information] \n\nWe may share your information with third parties in the following circumstances: \n\n- With vendors, consultants, and other service providers who need access to such information to carry out work on our behalf \n- In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with any applicable law, regulation, or legal process \n- If we believe your actions are inconsistent with the spirit or language of our user agreements or policies, or to protect the rights, property, and safety of [Insert company name] or others \n- In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company</string>
    <string name="TermsOfUse">These Terms of Use govern your access to and use of our mobile application (Coffee Community), including any content, functionality, and services offered on or through the App. \n\nBy using the App, you accept and agree to be bound and abide by these Terms and our Privacy Policy, incorporated herein by reference. If you do not want to agree to these Terms or the Privacy Policy, you must not access or use the App. \n\n1. The App is intended for users who are 13 years of age or older. By using this App, you represent and warrant that you are of legal age to form a binding contract with [Insert company name]. If you are not at least 13 years old, you must not access or use the App. \n\n2. We may revise and update these Terms from time to time in our sole discretion. All changes are effective immediately when we post them and apply to all access to and use of the App thereafter. Your continued use of the App following the posting of revised Terms means that you accept and agree to the changes. \n\n3. We reserve the right to withdraw or amend the App, and any service or material we provide on the App, in our sole discretion and without notice. We will not be liable if for any reason all or any part of the App is unavailable at any time or for any period. From time to time, we may restrict access to some parts of the App, or the entire App, to users, including registered users. \n\n4. You are responsible for making all arrangements necessary for you to have access to the App and for ensuring that all persons who access the App through your internet connection are aware of these Terms and comply with them. \n\n5. To access the App or some of its resources, you may be asked to provide certain registration details or other information. It is a condition of your use of the App that all information you provide is correct, current, and complete. You agree that all information you provide to register with this App or otherwise, including through the use of any interactive features on the App, is governed by our Privacy Policy and you consent to all actions we take with respect to your information consistent with our Privacy Policy.</string>
</resources>